<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Panic Button</string>

    <!-- Main menu -->
    <string name="choose_emergency_contacts">Choose emergency contacts</string>
    <string name="customize_help_message">Customize help message</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="choose_contacts">Choose Contacts</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="clear_icon">{fa-remove}</string>

    <string name="show_instructions">Show instructions</string>
    <string name="instructions">Instructions</string>
    <string name="choose_contacts_instructions">
        In order for this app to work, you need to choose one or more emergency contacts.
        When you activate the panic button, the app will text these contacts with a help message and your current location.
        You can review these instructions at any time by clicking the info icon in the toolbar above.
    </string>

    <!-- For show request rationale -->
    <string name="read_contacts_explanation">
        You need to give us access to your phone book,
        so you can choose emergency contacts.
    </string>
    <string name="send_sms_explanation">
        You need to allow us to send SMS messages on your behalf,
        so we can automatically alert your emergency contacts when you need help.
    </string>
    <string name="location_access_explanation">
        You need to give us access to your location,
        so we can tell your emergency contacts where you are when you need help.
    </string>
    <string name="location_services_explanation">
        You need to enable location services, so we can figure out where you are when you need help.
        Would you like to turn them on now?
    </string>
    <string name="enable_location_services">Enable Location Services</string>

    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="need_a_contact">In order for this app to work, you must choose at least one emergency contact.</string>

    <string name="default_help_message">I am in danger! Please send help!</string>

    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="welcome_message">
        You have now set up Panic Button.
        To further customize your Panic Button settings, click the buttons in the toolbar above.
    </string>

    <string name="help_message">Help message</string>
    <string name="help_message_hint">
        This is what is texted to your emergency contacts alongside your location
        when you activate Panic Button.
    </string>
    <string name="panic_instructions">Hit the big red button to start broadcasting for help.</string>
</resources>
